[{"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " oh my god! you cleaned!  look at these floors! you did the windows! oh, i have been begging you for months and you did! you cleaned! and nagging works!", "answer": " y&#146;know uh, i didn&#146;t actually do this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " oh no, was i cleaning in my sleep again?", "answer": " no, it wasn&#146;t you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " well then who?", "answer": " i got a maid. yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": "  i hope by maid you mean mistress, because if some other woman was here cleaning then&#133;", "answer": " uh honey, i know you don&#146;t like to relinquish control&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh, relinquish is just a fancy word for lose!", "answer": " look, she&#146;s really nice. okay? and she mentioned that she adored the way that you arranged the sponges.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " did she really say that?", "answer": " yes, i distinctly remember &#145;cause i thought it was a joke. now just give her a chance, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " fine, i can do it.  whew.", "answer": " what&#146;s the matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  who&#146;s cell phone is that? it&#146;s just so annoying; everywhere you go.", "answer": " i think it&#146;s coming from your bag.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  i never get calls!!  hello?", "answer": " hi, it&#146;s eric. from the halloween party, ursula&#146;s fianc\u008fe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " oh my god eric hi! wait, how&#146;d you get this number?", "answer": " oh, i have a friend who&#146;s a cop and he got it for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " wow! what an incredible violation&#151;and wonderful surprise.", "answer": " uh listen, i just&#151;i thought you should know i broke up with ursula.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh you did?  he did it! he did it!", "answer": " wow! what did he do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " shhh! i&#146;m talking.", "answer": " anyway, i was wondering if, you were the sort of person who&#133;eats lunch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " are you asking me out? &#145;cause it would be kinda weird since you just broke up with my sister.", "answer": " yeah uh&#133;okay. i&#146;m-i&#146;m sorry. bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " no! wait! i was just saying that so you&#146;d think i was a good person. fight for me.", "answer": " uhh, i won&#146;t take no for an answer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " not great, but we can work on it at lunch. okay, i can be at your apartment in two hours.", "answer": " great! but wh-wh&#151;how do you know where i live?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " i&#146;ve got friends too. okay, bye.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " so apparently i&#146;m available for lunch.", "answer": " i can&#146;t. i&#146;m busy. i&#146;m apartment hunting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " you&#146;re moving?", "answer": " yeah, i can&#146;t live with joey once the baby comes. i don&#146;t want my child&#146;s first words to be,  &quot;how you doin&#146;?&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " so does-does joey know you&#146;re moving?", "answer": " well, i haven&#146;t discussed it with him yet, but i know he&#146;s gonna be relieved. last week, he brought this girl over and i started talking to her about morning sickness and then i showed her pictures from my pregnancy book.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " that&#146;s not really porn.", "answer": " not so much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " hey, y&#146;know what and if you&#146;re looking for a place? i just heard in the elevator this morning that a woman in my building died.", "answer": " oh my god! was she old? does she have a view?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " well i don&#146;t know, but how-how great would that be huh? you living in my building. i could help take care of the baby. i can come over whenever i want.  with your permission.", "answer": " yeah that would really be great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " well can we see it?! oh maybe we shouldn&#146;t. i mean if she just died this morning out of respect.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " shall we?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " yes?", "answer": " hi. i&#146;m ross geller. i live in the building.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " and i&#146;m rachel, an admirer of the building.", "answer": " i-i heard about mrs. verhoeven passing away and i&#146;m so sorry for your loss. mrs. verhoeven's daughter: she didn&#146;t pass.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " what? mrs. verhoeven's daughter: my mother&#146;s still alive.", "answer": " oh, thank god! mrs. verhoeven's daughter: it looked like we were gonna lose her this morning, but she&#146;s a tough old bird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " ahh. mrs. verhoeven's daughter: are you close with her?", "answer": " of course! uh yeah, she and i would talk all the time in-in  the laundry room.  mrs. verhoeven's daughter: you speak dutch?  zeer vereerd een vriend van mijn moeder te ontmoeten.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " y&#146;know i would it&#146;s just painful.", "answer": " so she&#146;s really not dead. mrs. verhoeven's daughter: no, she&#146;s hanging in there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " mrs. bing, this tile cleaner is incredible! where&#146;d you get it?", "answer": " oh well umm, i make it myself! it&#146;s two parts ammonia and one part lemon juice. and now the secret ingredient is&#133;y&#146;know what? we just met.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " okay. uhh, i&#146;m gonna go get the clothes from the laundry room now. and, when i come back i&#146;ll clean behind the refrigerator.", "answer": "  i love her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " i&#146;ll be back in a minute.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " see? i told you.", "answer": " she stole my jeans!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": "  what?", "answer": " i have been looking for them all week and she is wearing them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " so she stole your pants and then she came back and wore them in front of you?", "answer": " don&#146;t you see? it&#146;s the perfect crime!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " she must&#146;ve been planning this for years!", "answer": " i will prove it to you! okay? about a week ago i was wearing those jeans and i dropped a pen in my lap and it left an ink stain on the crotch. now when she comes back i will find it and show you that stain!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " honey, isn&#146;t it possible that the company that sold the jeans made more than just the one pair?", "answer": " i guess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " so, shouldn&#146;t we go give her the benefit of the doubt before we go&#133;snooping around her crotch?", "answer": " fine. i&#146;m just glad i didn&#146;t give her my secret ingredient.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " out of curiosity, what is your secret ingredient?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " come in, i&#146;m so glad you&#146;re here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " yeah, me too. not in the shaky angry way you are though.", "answer": " sorry, i just saw ursula. i had to give the engagement ring back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " just seeing her brought it all back. all the lies, the way she used me. i just&#133;i got so angry just looking at her&#133;&#133;face.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " yeah.  yeah.", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry. i just&#133;when i look at you i see her. when i see her i get a little bit angry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " maybe this is too weird.", "answer": " no wait! there&#146;s only a problem when i look at you.  oh i got it! i got it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " no don&#146;t tear out your eyes!!", "answer": " i was just, i was just gonna take out my lenses.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " oh, yeah try that.  so, is that better?", "answer": " not really. you&#133;you&#146;re blurry, but you still look like ursula. you&#146;re blursula. okay wait. maybe&#133;if i-if i just don&#146;t look at you for a while.  see? it&#133;it works. i&#146;m not, i&#146;m not angry at all anymore! this is a great date!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " yeah, we&#146;re done.", "answer": " ezel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": "  hey ross! listen, do you want to go see that new imax movie on tide pools?", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  no. but i got knicks tickets for you, me, and chandler.", "answer": " sweet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " all right, well finish your coffee; let&#146;s go.", "answer": " okay i-i just have to stop by my place first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " to tape the game? you do this every time ross, you&#146;re not gonna be on tv!", "answer": " no-no, i-i have to see if this apartment became available.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh, you&#146;re switching apartments?", "answer": " it&#146;s not for me, it&#146;s for rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " but rachel has an apartment.", "answer": " yeah, but when the baby comes she&#146;s gonna want to move.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " she is?", "answer": " yeah, you didn&#146;t expect her to live there with a baby did you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " i guess i didn&#146;t really think about it.", "answer": "  ezel!  hey gunther! you&#146;re an ezel! gunther: jij hebt seks met ezels.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " nice jeans!", "answer": " oh thanks! i like your top.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " what happened?!", "answer": " oh, i fell asleep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " i was thinking about taking my lunch break.", "answer": " oh, will you do the top of the cabinets? that&#146;ll really work up your appetite for lunch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": " what&#146;s going on?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " how was the game?", "answer": " oh, okay. i&#133;i ate way too much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " ooh.  so umm, i was talkin&#146; to ross and he said you were looking for a new place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " oh yeah! hopefully across the street if certain dutch people would just let go.", "answer": " i was kinda hoping you&#146;d stay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh but joey, i have to go. there&#146;s no room for a baby here.", "answer": " no room? it&#146;s a baby. it&#146;s like this big.  y&#146;know, i mean you-you could you could put it over here.  or-or-or we could put it right here.  aw, it&#146;s cute, right? or-or we could put it over here.  you wouldn&#146;t even notice it. where&#146;s the baby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " honey, it&#146;s not just a matter of where you put it. i mean a baby changes everything. they cry all the time. i mean imagine bringing home some girl and trying to score when there&#146;s a screaming baby around.", "answer": " i could use a challenge! it&#146;s getting pretty easy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " honey, it&#146;s so sweet that you want me to stay, but i-i can&#146;t do that to you. i mean it would disrupt your entire life.", "answer": " i love living with you so much. i just wish things didn&#146;t have to change.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " y&#146;know i blame ross for this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " i do too a little bit.", "answer": " i&#146;m gonna miss you, you&#146;re the hottest roommate i ever had.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " ooh, oh no! i have to go! i have a massage appointment.", "answer": " oh no, stay here we&#146;ll keep doing this. i&#146;ll pay you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " no, i got in trouble for that before. i&#146;ll see you later.", "answer": " absolutely.  i love the way you kiss.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " hey! umm, i think brenda needs a raise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " how come?", "answer": " because i put my head between her legs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " to see her pants?", "answer": " they&#146;re my pants!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " are you sure? did you see the stain?", "answer": " no! i was just getting into position and then everything went dark.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " god! she is not stealing from us! okay, will you let this go?", "answer": " fine.  she&#146;s wearing my bra!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh dear god!", "answer": " my pink flowered bra! i recognize the strap!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " and yet you don&#146;t recognize that you&#146;re crazy.", "answer": " here&#146;s the plan! okay? i&#146;m going to leave you get a look at brenda&#146;s bra!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " here&#146;s another plan&#133;no!", "answer": " i would do it but she thinks i&#146;m attracted to her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " did you not hear where my head was? come on! come on we&#146;re a team! we&#146;re in this together!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i fear a jury will see it the same way!", "answer": " do this for me! come on, i catch you looking at woman&#146;s breasts all the time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " you see that?", "answer": " do you see this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " all right. yes. okay. i get your point. but if it&#146;s not your bra will you just let the woman clean the apartment?!", "answer": " yes! absolutely. okay? look, you&#146;ll know it&#146;s mine because on the right cup, the lacey part, there&#146;s a very noticeable rip.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " hi. how is she? mrs. verhoeven's daughter: it&#146;s not looking good.", "answer": "  oh.  oh. well i uh, i brought her some bloemen.  mrs. verhoeven's daughter: that&#146;s so sweet.  would you like to come in and say good-bye? i&#146;m sure it would mean a lot to her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " oh i don&#146;t know that it would. mrs. verhoeven's daughter: well, her memory is pretty much gone.", "answer": " all right then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " welcome back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " hey!  can we pick up where we left off?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, i&#146;m still pretty tired out from this afternoon.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " uh, the sex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " what sex?", "answer": " our sex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " we didn&#146;t have sex.", "answer": " well if i didn&#146;t have sex with you, i had sex with someone that looked an awful lot like&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": "  ew! ew! ew! ew! ew! ew!", "answer": "  oh no! oh no! oh no! oh no! no! no! no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " you-you&#133;you had sex with ursula?!", "answer": " uh, a little bit. she-she-she walked in and i thought she was you and i kissed her and&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " you didn&#146;t notice she was wearing different clothes?!", "answer": " well i was just so excited to see you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh. ew! ew! ew! ugh! y&#146;know what? this is too weird.", "answer": " no-no it&#146;s not! i don&#146;t want to lose you! it&#146;s-it&#146;s like i was saying to ursula when i was making love to her and i thought she was you&#151;yeah it is too weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " so i guess this is it.", "answer": " yeah.  maybe it&#146;s for the best. you smell just like her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": "  what are you doing?", "answer": " i&#146;m leaning. this is where i lean.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " okay. (goes over and fluffs up the pillows on the couch.", "answer": " brenda a bee!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " yes! it&#146;s flown into your blouse and you&#146;d better undo your buttons lest it sting you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " i think i know what&#146;s going on here.", "answer": " you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " look, i know it must be hard that your wife is a lesbian, but it&#146;s wrong. you&#146;re married.", "answer": " i totally understand.  can i just see your bra?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": "  where did you get those jeans?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " you gave them to me!", "answer": " no i didn&#146;t!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " all right, i took them. but i figured it would be okay because you got a big ink stain on the crotch.", "answer": " oh no! did you take my bra too?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " what bra?", "answer": " the pink one with the flowers?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " what is this?", "answer": " hey! uh, this is just to give you an idea. okay well, we can put screens here,  so that the baby has privacy, and-and-and maybe a mobile over the crib. and uh&#151;oh look! here&#146;s a baby monitor , which until the baby comes we can use as walkie-talkies. huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " but joey the baby is going to be crying, it&#146;s going to be loud.", "answer": " i&#146;m loud!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " it&#146;s gonna be up all night!", "answer": " i&#146;m up all night!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " it&#146;s gonna poop!", "answer": " hello!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " what about all the women you want to bring home?", "answer": " look, if i&#146;m bringing home a woman who can&#146;t stand being around a baby, then maybe i don&#146;t want to be with that woman! or maybe we&#146;ll just do it in the bathroom of the club!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " joey, are you sure?", "answer": " yeah! all right&#151;look, i know sometimes it&#146;ll be hard, okay? but, it&#146;ll also be really&#133;really great. please rachel! i-i-i really want you to stay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " i want me to stay too.", "answer": " ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " thank you.  oh joey and look at this crib! it&#146;s so cute!", "answer": " i know! i found it on the street.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " are you serious&#151;really?! it&#146;s in such good condition.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " wow! whoa-whoa what&#146;s under the covers?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " it&#146;s moving.", "answer": " ew.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " it&#146;s still&#151;&#151;it&#146;s got a tail! get it out of here! get it out of here!!", "answer": " ooh! ah! okay!  dedicated to the memory of pearl harmon", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " well, the old lady died. and how do i know? her dying wish was for one last kiss. but i don&#146;t care,  because you got the apartment. yes!", "answer": " ewww. yeah. umm. i think i&#146;m gonna stay here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " isn&#146;t that great?", "answer": "  ezels!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}]